jollibeedelivery.com 2017-11-21

# Jollibee Delivery

We may collect the following information:

Name  
Contact information including email address  
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers for the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

Internal record keeping.  
We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [online.store@jollibee.com.ph.](mailto:online.store@jollibee.com.ph)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 6F Jollibee Plaza 10 F. Ortigas, Jr. Ave. Ortigas Center, Pasig City 1650 Philippines.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE NAME | COOKIE DESCRIPTION  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CART | Your preferred currency  
CURRENCY | The association with your shopping cart.  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | The association with your shopping cart.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
Back to Previous Page

We may collect the following information:

Name  
Contact information including email address  
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers for the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

Internal record keeping.  
We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [online.store@jollibee.com.ph.](mailto:online.store@jollibee.com.ph)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 6F Jollibee Plaza 10 F. Ortigas, Jr. Ave. Ortigas Center, Pasig City 1650 Philippines.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

<

COOKIE NAME | COOKIE DESCRIPTION  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CART | Your preferred currency  
CURRENCY | The association with your shopping cart.  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | The association with your shopping cart.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
Back to Previous Page

Unless otherwise defiend elsewhere in these Site Terms and Conditions, the following terms shall have the meanings ascribed to below:

  * Trademarks \- This Site contains many of the valuable trademarks owned and used by Jollibee Foods Corporation and its subsidiaries and affiliates throughout the world to distinguish its quality products and services. These trademarks and related proprietary property are protected from copying and simulation under national and international laws and are not to be used, reproduced, adapted (whether in its original form or derivations thereof) or copied without the express written permission of Jollibee Foods Corporation. 
  * Privacy Policy \- Standard legal terms on privacy policy of Jollibee of data that may be collected by website visitors or customers. 
  * Website \- By entering this Site, you acknowledge and agree that the use of this Site is at your own risk and to the extent permissible by applicable law, under no circumstances shall Jollibee Foods Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, representatives, agents, contractors and consultants (collectively referred to as “JFC”) be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, losses, costs or expenses nor for any loss of profit that results from the use of, or inability to use this Site or any material on any site linked to this Site (including but not limited to any viruses or any other errors or defects or failures in computer transmissions or network communications) even if JFC has been advised of the possibility of such damage. 

If you decide to register with this Site, you will be asked to create an account and provide your personal information and register a password. You must keep this password confidential and must not disclose it to anyone. If you believe someone else knows your password, please change your password immediately.Jollibee reserves the right to suspend your registration if you breach these Terms and Conditions.

  1. These Terms and Conditions shall apply to all orders of “Jollibee products” (“Products”) to our Customers. All orders for the Products shall be deemed to be an offer by the customer to purchase the Products in accordance with these Terms.
  2. Acceptance of Orders. The acceptance of orders for the Products shall be at the entire discretion of Jollibee. Our acceptance of an order occurs when you receive an on-screen message or email message confirming your order has been placed at which point, your contract with JFC is made and up until this point. JFC reserves the right to decline to deliver the Products without giving any reason. 
    1. Trading time for Credit card will be available from 7am to 9pm only
    2. Minimum food purchase of P200.00
    3. 30 minutes guarantee: 
      * applies to single receipt transaction amounting to P1,100 and below - excludes more than 20 orders per transaction of the same product combinations
      * Customer will be given P200 Jollibee Gift Certificate if the 30 minutes guarantee is not met. The 30 minutes guarantee is based on the agreed, synchronized time of the agent with the customer.
    4. Orders P1,101 to P2,000 will be served 45 minutes without guarantee. 
    5. Choice of Chicken part is subject to availability.
  3. You may not place any orders on Our Web Site if you are under 12 years of age. 
  4. Order Confirmation. Your Order Confirmation is a record of our agreement to deliver the Products ordered and paid for in full. If another person ordered Products on your behalf and using your account, you agree that such order shall be considered as your own, and shall be subject to these Terms. 
  5. Changes of Orders. If you wish to cancel, amend or complain about your order, please call the Jollibee Hotline (#87000), details of which will be included in the confirmatory e-mail sent to you upon placing your order. If you change your order, the price charged will be the price for the amended order. If you pay by credit card the price difference will need to be paid separately to Jollibee or any refund would need to be processed by our Customer Services team who can be contacted here. Please note that as promotions are only available for limited periods, any changes to your order may mean the promotions are no longer available.Change of orders or delivery time can be made no later than 5 minutes prior to the start of the delivery window booked.Change of order can be made up to 5 minutes before the delivery window begins. Amends to the order must be made by phoning the store direct. Your initial payment will be cancelled and a new payment raised.The delivery time slot may be altered up to 5 minutes before the start of your order window. The order can only be changed to a new time slot if it is available. 
  6. Cancellations of Orders. Orders may be cancelled in full up to 5 minutes before the start of the delivery window selected. We will endeavor to issue a refund to your credit card account within 3 weeks. Cancellations within 5 minutes of the start of the delivery window will be charged in full. 

JFC offers delivery services within Metro Manila, Pampanga, Cavite and Cebu. A “Jollibee” store only has a limited delivery area. If your location is NOT within a delivery area, you will be advised by our Call Center. 

  1. Unless otherwise stated in writing the prices quoted on this web site are inclusive of value-added and any other applicable taxes.
  2. You may refer to the site (by clicking the checkout button) to check the price of the Product/s you wish to order. Without prejudice to any inadvertent technical mistake (which will be charged to the customer), the price of the Product/s shall be as reflected on the site. The price for your order shall be deducted from your account at the time your order is placed. We reserve our right to refuse to deliver any order if for what ever reason we believe that payment will be refused at any stage.
  3. You can pay by any of the methods listed in our checkout screen. Please make sure that if your order is placed using a credit, such card is valid on the date of dispatch of your order.
  4. Payment Methods. We accept the following forms of payment:CashCredit / Charge cards: Visa and Mastercard are accepted.

Upon submission of your order details, you are making an offer to us to purchase the item(s) you have specified in your order form. We reserve the right to refuse your offer should it be necessary. In the event a refund is necessary, JFC shall exert reasonable efforts to credit your account within 3 weeks. 

  1. JFC shall exert reasonable efforts to meet your requested delivery time. It is understood, however, that delay due to traffic, inclement weather or similar or analogous conditions are beyond JFC’s control and should not at any time be taken against JFC.
  2. You agree to accept delivery of the Products at the agreed time and place of delivery.
  3. JFC can only fulfill an order of up to P2,000.
  4. Present your Valid ID to our rider upon receipt of goods, for verification for credit card transactions.

You understand that Product/s are subject to availability at the time of delivery. If the Products you ordered are not available, JFC may offer you a reasonable substitute (Product of equivalent quality and price) or we may advise you through phone call (local Philippines) or electronic mail (outside Philippines) for alternative Product/s. You understand that should you choose to order other Product/s, this may affect the purchase price. 

_Note: For Advance Order please call #87000_

From time to time, Products may be subject to special offers. Any special offer shall be subject to these Terms. In case of inconsistency between the special offer and these Terms, the latter shall prevail. JFC reserves the right to amend the conditions and/or availability of special offers, or withdraw them at its discretion. However, JFC will honor any order received before the withdrawal or amendment of the offer, without prejudice to any inadvertent technical mistake (which will be charged to the customer).All special offers are valid only within the promotional period, are subject to change and are not valid in conjunction with other offers, unless otherwise stated.

JFC shall not be liable for any loss, expense, cost or damage arising out arising directly or indirectly out of or in connection with delay beyond the estimated time or date of delivery, availability of Product/s at any given time, force majeure, and any circumstances beyond JFC’s control, and over which JFC could not have avoided even with the exercise of reasonable care, or any indirect or unforeseeable loss suffered or incurred by customers or third parties. In any event, JFC’s liability for any given transaction shall not exceed the total price charged for the relevant items. The products ordered should be consumed not later than one (1) hour from actual receipt, we will not be liable for any event that may arise as a result/consequence of products consumed beyond the specified time.
